（山村）＜俺の名前は山村和也。→
My name is Yamamura Kazuya.
今　俺はモーレツに緊張している。→
Right now, I am violently nervous!
そう憧れていた存在に　ようやく
会う事が出来るからだ＞
Yes! And it's because I am finally
able to meet with the one I idolize!
（不良達）げえ！
（男鹿）オラオラオラオラ！
うが～！
（ベル坊）ダーブー！！
（山村）待って下さい！
Please, wait!
（山村）男鹿さん　お願いです！
Oga-san, please listen!
どうか　この俺を
弟分にして下さい！
Please accept me as your
sworn little brother!
お願いします！
Please!
あ～ん？見てんじゃねえよ！
Whatcha lookin' at?! I'll bust you up!
ぶっつぶすぞ！
う～ん　なんか違うな。
Something's off...
こうか？いや…それとも→
Like this?
No...
Or maybe... like this?!
こんな感じか！？
＜俺の名前は山村和也。
聖石矢魔学園に通う→
My name is Yamamura Kazuya.
I attend St. Ishiyama Academy
as a first-year student.
１年にして目下　不良の修行中＞
I am currently training to be a delinquent.
＜夏休みデビューなんて
クラスのヤツは笑うが→
The guys in class laughed at me when
I came out during summer break.
言いたいヤツには
言わせておけばいい＞
They can talk all they want.
＜俺は変わると決めたんだ＞
Because I've decided to change myself!
＜そう！強くなると＞
That's right! I'll make myself stronger!
《ここが男鹿さんち。
思ったより普通だな》
This is Oga-san's house.
It's a lot more normal than I thought.
Oga
《てっきり　こんな感じかと
思ってたけど…》
Honestly, I thought it'd be more like this.
《案外　家族は
普通の人たちなのかも》
Maybe his family is actually pretty normal?
《いやいや　油断しない方がいい》
No-no... I shouldn't let down my guard.
《どんな化け物が出てくるか》
Who knows what monsters might show up!
ダーアア！
ぎゃああああ！
うお！
《やっぱり心の準備は必要だな》
ふんむ！
Yeah... Looks like I need
to mentally prepare myself.
（ピンポーン）
（ヒルダ）は～い　ただいま。
Yes, coming!
《予想外のキター！》
Now this was unexpected!
She cometh! She cometh! She cometh!
アーッ！
どちら様でしょうか？
And who might you be?
グ　グッモーニン。
G-Good morning...
ん？
May I Call You Brother?
お初に　お目にかかります。
姐さん！
It is a pleasure to meet you, Sister.
自分　今日から男鹿さんの弟分
やらせていただきます→
My name is Yamamura Kazuya
and starting today,
山村和也と申します。
I shall take the role of
Oga-san's sworn little brother!
男鹿さんの奥さんですね。
以後　お見知りおきを。
You are Oga-san's wife, are you not? I
am pleased to make your acquaintance.
ほう…ほうほう　弟分。
Sworn little brother?
てめえ　マジで来たのかよ。
You seriously came here?
男鹿さん！お迎えにあがりました。
Oga-san, I have come to walk you to school!
弟分というと家来のことだな。
Sworn little brother...
You serve him then, yes?
少しは出世したではないか。
It looks like you've moved up in the world!
ダァァ！
そんなんじゃねえよ。
That ain't it.
いってらっしゃいませ～。
Have a lovely day!
は～い。
Thank you!
なんだありゃ！？
ダーブー。
What the heck...
いや～さすが　アニキ。
Brother, you are so incredible!
まさか奥さんが外国の方とは。
To think your wife would be a foreigner!
しかも　すんごいグラマー美人！
あっカバン持ちます！
And she's an incredibly busty beauty!
Oh! Let me carry your bag.
あのな～昨日から言ってんだろ。
Now, see here... I've been
telling you since yesterday.
俺はアニキじゃね～し。
ついてくんなっつ～の！
I ain't your brother or whatever,
so stop following me!
しっしっ！
ウィッウィッ。
そんなぁ～待ってくださいよ。
アニキ～。
Don't be like that.
Please wait, Brother!
《ったく…なんなんだ　こいつ
妙に　なつきやがって》
Man, what's with him?
He's taken a pretty creepy liking to me...
《これ以上　自由を
奪われてたまるか》
I don't need any less freedom!
だいたい…！えっと。
ああ！カズっす！
Look here, uh...
Oh, call me Kazu!
カズは何年なんだよ！
What year are you, Kazu?
１年です。１年６組１５番。
I'm a first year. First year, class 6, #15!
ほら見ろ！
俺と同い年じゃねえか。
See? You're the same age as me.
つまりだ　ここから
導き出される答えは…。
And therefore we can conclude...
俺は　お前のお兄ちゃんではない！
ダー！
I am not your older brother!
いや　そりゃまあ。
Well, uh...
でも俺　男鹿さんの強さに
本気で憧れてるんす！
But I really do look up
to your strength, Oga-san!
不良の間じゃ　もはや伝説ですよ！
マジで！
You're already legendary among delinquents!
たった１人で　あの石矢魔を
制した最強の１年生！
You're the strongest first year ever!
The top of the notorious Ishiyama High!
強くなりたいんです！
俺も男鹿さんみたいに！
I want to become stronger
just like you, Oga-san!
そんな男鹿さんを
アニキと呼ぶのは当然っす！
It is only natural that I call
you Brother out of respect!
いえ　呼ばせて下さい！
No, I beg you for the privilege!
ん～！しょうがないな～もう。
ダッイー。
Ah, I suppose if you insist...
（ピッ）
（古市）で　結局　連れてきたのかよ。
So in the end you brought him with you.
（古市）はっきり言うぞ。バカだろ。
ＮＯ！バカじゃない。アニキだ。
I'm going say this straight.
Are you an idiot?
I no idiot. I honorary brother!
（古市）バカアニキ！
アナタ　つなげる　よくない。
Honorary brother idiot!
Those words go together not!
（古市）あのなぁ神崎や姫川じゃ
ね～んだ。弟分なんて。
Look he ain't Kanzaki or Himekawa...
Your sworn little brother?
（山村）古市さんですよね！
そ　そうだけど。
You're Furuichi-san, yes?
Y-Yes, and...?
すげえ！噂は本当だったんだ！
噂？
Amazing! The rumors are true!
Rumors?
男鹿さんの相棒にして
唯一つっこめる男　智将　古市！
Oga-san's one faithful companion...
The only man who can talk back to him!
Furuichi the Strategist!
イケメンで頭も切れるとか！
超カッコいいっす！
Handsome and with a sharp mind!
You're super cool!
He's a great guy!
《いいヤツじゃないか》
《だろ？》
See?
（チャイム）
（梓）へ～男鹿さんの弟分に
してもらったんだ。
Oh? So you're Oga-san's sworn little brother?
よかったね！和くん！
おう！まあな！
Good for you, Kazu-kun!
Yeah, guess so!
だが問題は　これからだ。
弟分になったからって→
But the difficult part begins now.
Just being his sworn little brother
isn't going to make me stronger.
即強くなれるわけじゃ
ないからな。
これからは厳しい修行の毎日！
From now on, it's harsh training every day!
やっぱ目標はあの必殺技
８００ボルトの電撃だな。
My goal is definitely that special attack...
...the 800 volt shock!
((ダーーッ！！))
だけど和くん　そんなに
強くなって　どうするの？
But wait, Kazu-kun... Why do
you want to get so strong?
は？そりゃ男は　やっぱ
強くなきゃダメだろ。
Huh? Cause being a guy, you
gotta be strong, right?
拳ひとつで世の中
渡っていくっつ～か？
Travel the world using only your
fists, and stuff like that.
あのね　和くん。
あ？
Now look here, Kazu-kun. There's
all different kinds of strength.
強さにも色々あるんだよ。
先週のアニメごはん君でも
言ってたんだから！
That's what last week's Gohan-kun anime said!
はあ？
強さは愛！ときどきコロッケ！
Strength is love! And sometimes croquettes!
意味わかんねえよ。
What's that supposed to mean?
おっと！こんな事してる場合じゃ
ねえ。アニキんとこ行かなきゃ！
Crap, I don't have time for this!
I gotta go see my brother!
（ざわめき）
あむ！
んぐんぐ…。
《やっぱ…強さはコロッケ》
Strength really is croquettes?
《そういえばコロッケを初めて
食べた日本人は→
Now that I think about it, wasn't Mito
Mitsukuni the first Japanese to eat a croquette?
たしか水戸光圀　つまり水戸黄門》
Also know as Mito Koumon.
Mito Koumon was a Vice-Shogun during the Edo Period
《コロッケというものには
もともと人を土下座させる→
Perhaps there really is a mysterious power in
croquettes that makes people grovel before you...
不思議なパワーが
備わっているのかも》
《いや　待てよ…水戸黄門が食べた
のは　ラーメンだったっけか？》
Or wait... Wasn't it ramen that he ate?
はぐはぐ…。
えっと　君　大丈夫？
Um, are you okay over there?
ああっ　すみません！
アニキのように強くなるために→
I'm sorry!
In order to become strong like you, Brother,
I thought I should mimic exactly what you do!
アニキの一挙手一投足を
まねようと思って。
ほら　門前の小僧　習わぬ　経を読む
っていうじゃないですか。
They say, "learn by doing", yes?
しょんべんの小僧？
いや　門前の小僧…な。
Learn by pooing?
No... by doing!
どうでもいいから　メシ位
ゆっくり食わせろよ。
Whatever, just let me eat in peace!
ダーブー。
（邦枝）お　男鹿。
あ？
ダア？
O-Oga...
ちょ…ちょちょちょっと。
C-Could you...
つきあいなさいよ。
...go out with me.
（不良達）ハッ！
（不良達）うおおおお～！！
（真田弟）
クイーンが男鹿を誘ったああ！
The Queen asked Oga out!
（真田兄）ついに愛の告白かあ！
Her confession of love is finally here!
（寧々）姐さん！早まっちゃ
いけません！
Madame, you mustn't be too hasty!
（真田兄弟）ヒューヒュー！
《中学生か！このクラス》
Is everyone here in elementary school?!
（邦枝）ち　違うわよ！生活指導の
先生に呼び出されたの！
T-That's not what I meant!
I've been summoned by the guidance counselor.
あんたも一緒にね！
お　おい！
And so have you!
Hey!
（邦枝）失礼します。
Pardon us.
（木戸）生活指導の木戸です。
I am Kido, the guidance counselor.
君たち　なぜ　ここに
呼び出されたかは　わかってるね？
I suspect you know why I've
called you here today.
ダブゥ？
ん？
いや…君じゃない。
ダブー。
No, not you.
まったくおそれいったよ。
転入早々暴力事件とは。
I was afraid of this. The second you
transferred in, we have a violent incident.
帝毛工業の生徒達と派手に
やらかしてくれたそうじゃないか。
I hear that you two did a real number
on some students from Teimo Tech.
それは　あいつらの方が先…。
君らを退学にするのは簡単だ。→
But they were the ones that...
It would be trivial to expel you.
…が　それでは　うちに
来てもらった意味がない。
But then there would be no
reason for you to be here now.
そこでだ。
聞けば君たちは石矢魔でも→
And there it is. I have heard you are like
Ishiyama's leaders or something, yes?
リーダー的存在だと
いうじゃないか。
はあ！？
どういう意味でしょうか？
What do you mean?
フッ…名付けて石矢魔再生計画。
I call it... The Ishiyama
Reformation Project.
立ち聞きは良くないよ！？
梓！？
Listening in on people isn't right!
Azusa?
それとも「メイドさんは見た！」
ごっことか？
Or are you re-enacting a scene
from "Ms. Maid saw you"?
メイドの土産に聞かせてやろう！
This maid shall tell you before you perish!
お前達のやったことは全部
お見通しだ！
I've seen through everything
you people are plotting!
ちょ…静かにしろ。
B-Be quiet.
ようするに　うちの連中が
悪さしないように→
In other words, it's our job
to keep everyone in line.
取締役になれってことよね。
あ？そうなの？
It is?
まったく…退学を脅しに
使ったりして感じ悪いわね。
I don't like that guy, threatening
us with expulsion...
《男鹿と２人で学級委員的役目》
It's like Oga and I are on
the Student Council together!
《放課後の教室で２人で
学級日誌を書いたりとか→
After school, the two of us in the
classroom writing the daily journal...
誰もいない校舎を
２人きりで見回ったりとか》
Just the two of us making the
rounds in the school building!
ち　違う！別に私は
そんなつもりで。
N-No! T-That's not what I intend...
ったく　めんどくせ～。
ダーブー。
Man, what a pain.
まっ後は任せたわ。
はあ！？
Well, I'll let you handle the rest!
ちょっ　何　言ってんの！
待ちなさいよ！
What are you saying? Hold it!
はあ～もう最悪。
This sucks...
あ…昨日の。
You're the one from yesterday.
昨日は危ないところを
ありがとうございました。
Thank you for saving me yesterday.
い　いえ…いいのよ。
Oh, don't worry about it.
アニキがいつも
お世話になってます。
Thank you for always assisting my brother!
ご挨拶が遅れました。
俺は山村和也。
I apologize for not introducing
myself. I am Yamamura Kazuya.
カズって呼んで下さい。こいつは
幼なじみの藤崎梓っていって…。
Please call me Kazu.
This is my childhood
friend, Fujisaki Azusa...
だ～から幼なじみって
今どき恥ずかしくない？
Not again... Aren't you embarrassed
saying "childhood friend" at this point?
そこは　いいっつってんだろ！
It's fine, jeez!
それより早く戻らないと
昼休み　終わっちゃうよ。
Anyway, we have to get back
or lunch break will be over!
今日は日直でしょ？
やること　いっぱいあるんだから。
You've got day duty today, right?
《どうすれば　こんな風に　可愛く
男子と会話が出来るんだろう》
How can she do it? How can I talk
to a boy all cute like that?
《これまで　私の周りには
いなかったタイプだわ》
I've never had anyone like
her around me before...
ん？
《この子に　何か学ぶことが
あるかもしれない》
I might be able to learn something from her!
ねえ　ちょっといいかしら？
Hey. You got a minute?
ダーーーッ！
でや～っ！おりゃ～っ！
ダーブ。
[TV]（ゴハンくん）今日こそ　許さないぞ！
うんこ男爵！
Count Poo, today you aren't getting away!
Impertinent fool!
[TV]（うんこ男爵）こざかしい！
白米ごときに→
You seriously think some
white rice can defeat me?
私が倒されると思うのか！
Stop it, the both of you!
[TV]（おかずちゃん）２人とも落ちついて！
Brother, what shall I do next?
アニキ！次は
何しましょうか？
Uh, that's enough. You're damn loud.
いや　もういいから。
うるさいし。
そんなこと言わずに！
あ　じゃあ坊っちゃんのお世話を。
Oh, don't be like that!
Oh! Why don't I take care of the little guy?
ダー！ダー！
Seems like he don't want
you taking care of him.
お前には　世話されたくないそうだ。
ダー！
I see... Then, how about
I help make dinner, Ma'am?
そうすか。じゃあ　夕飯の
お手伝いします　お母さん。
えっ！？
（山村）コロッケ作りましょう　コロッケ！
Let's make croquettes!
いいから　お前もう帰れ！
うっとうしい！
Enough! Go home already.
You're a pest.
まあ　よいではないか。
弟分なのだろう？
What is so wrong with it? He's
your sworn little brother, yes?
（男鹿父）
ん？君は誰かね？
Who are you?
You're my brother's father, yes?
アニキのお父さんですか！よろしくお願いします！
It is a pleasure to meet you!
あ…アニキ
辰巳の弟なのか？
Brother?
Tatsumi's little brother?!
When did this happen?!
お前　いつの間に！？
父親は誰なんだ～！
WHO IS THE FATHER?!
Oh? So this is where you live, Senpai?
へぇ～！ここが先輩の
おうちなんですか！
Sorry for asking you out here like this...
悪かったわね
急に誘ったりして。
Naw... Kazu-kun's over
at Oga-san's house, so...
いえ！和くん
男鹿さん家に行っちゃったし。
（邦枝）
いつも一緒に帰ってるの？
Do you always walk home together?
It's not "always", but...
いつもってわけじゃないけど
家が近所だから？
'Cause he lives in the
neighborhood, you know?
Oh, right... He did say you
were childhood friends.
そ　そうなんだ
幼なじみって言ってたもんね。
《違う！こんな話をしに
来たんじゃない！どうすれば　→
No! This isn't what I
called her to talk about!
I need to ask her how she can talk with
boys in such a naturally cute manner!
あんな風に　自然にかわいく
男子に接することができるか→
それを　この子から
学び取らないと…》
I've got to learn this from her...
ん？
ところで　そ…その→
So anyway, are you two
like... d-d-dating, right?
ふ…ふたりは　やっぱり
つきあってるの？
Um... Could it be that you...
あの～　先輩ひょっとして。
え？
...have a crush on Kazu-kun?
（梓）和くんのこと
好きなんですか？
N-N-No! I...
な…ち　違う　私は。
そうですよね
そんなわけ　ないですよね。
Yeah... I figured it couldn't be that.
You've got Oga-san, after all.
先輩には　男鹿さんがいるし。
な　な～！！
そうだ！ちょうどいいから
和くんのこと→
I know! Since I'm here and all,
I'll pray to God for Kazu-kun!
神様にお願いしていこうっと！
I pray that Kazu-kun gets stronger.
和くんが強くなれますように！
《ダメだ　天然だ。
この子には　かなわない》
It's no use... She's naturally this way...
I can't hold a candle to her. I'll
never be able to act like that.
《絶対マネできない》
（チャイム）
もぐ…。
おそろいのお弁当！？
Matching lunches?
（真田兄弟）お～っ！
そういう関係か？
So that's how it is with you two!
You okay with this, Furuichi?
いいのか古市？
（真田兄弟）ヒューヒュー！
You really are like elementary schoolers...
だから中学生かって…。
Your mother taught me the
menu, and I made it myself!
アニキのお母さんに
メニュー教えてもらって→
自分で作ってきました！
Kazu... Isn't it about
time to give it a rest?
カズ　そろそろ
やめにしねえか？
But I want to become stronger!
でもオレ　強くなりたいんです。
アニキみたいに！→
Just like you!
If I can't learn by imitating,
then please teach me how to train!
門前の小僧がダメなら
修業の方法を教えて下さい。
Train me to unleash that special attack!
あの必殺技の電撃を出せる
修業を　オレに！
Train me!
よしっ　わかった！放課後
体育館裏に来い！特訓してやる！
Okay, got it! Meet me behind
the gymnasium after school.
I'll train you!
You will?
本当ですか？
Oh jeez, Oga...
おいおい　男鹿…。
Azusa, you're alone today?
梓　今日はひとり？
Yeah. Kazu-kun's got some
kind of training, he said.
うん。和くん特訓なんだって。
（坊主頭）ウーウー…。
ん？ウッ！
キャー！
ウー…。
はい～　そこで手を十字に組んで
「ジョワッ！」と叫んで！
Now, cross your arms and yell out "Jowa!"
ん…ジョワ！
Jowa!
Damn, that was close.
Put more spirit into it.
あ～惜しい。
そこ　もっと心を込めて。
（山村）ジョワッ！
Jowa!
ん～　手の角度が
ちょっと違う？
Maybe your arms are at
a slightly wrong angle?
大丈夫なのか？男鹿。
Are you sure about this, Oga?
Pretty soon Baby Beel'll
get hungry and peeved...
あぁ　そろそろベル坊が
腹をすかせて　ぐずり出す頃だ。
そうすれば…。
ジョワッ！
And when that happens...
Jowa!
ダーブ。
ちょ…それって　まさか？
Wait... You don't mean...
ジョワッ！
Jowa!
ビ…ギョエ。
ヒィー！
Now, put more energy into it!
はい～　そこでもっと
気合い入れて！
ジョワーーー！！
Jowa!!
ビェェェー！！
（古市）ギャー！！
All right! I finally learned
the secret shock attack!
やった！ついに　必殺の
電撃技を身に付けた！
Yes, excellent work!
うむ！よくやった！オレから
教えることは　もう何もない！
I have now taught you everything I know!
ダーブ！
♪～　フンフフフンフンフー
フンフフフンフンフー
♪～　フンフフフン…
あ…。
ウー！
あ～…。
♪～　フンフフフンフンフー
≪カズ！≫
Kazu!
大変だ！
We've got trouble!
藤崎が　何かイカつい顔した
坊主頭の男に→
Fujisaki's been carried off by a
rugged-looking man with a shaved head!
連れられていったぞ！
坊主頭？
Shaved head?
《まさか　帝毛のヤツらが
この前の復讐に？》
Don't tell me... Those Teimo
bastards are back for revenge?!
おい　どうすんだよ？
Hey, what'll we do?
ど　どうするって　そりゃ…。
W-What'll we do? Uh...
《助けないと…でも　オレ１人で？
アニキに助けを→
I have to save her...
But, alone? Should I ask my brother to help?
頼んだほうがいいか…》
It would be simple to expel you two...
（木戸）
((君らを退学にするのは簡単だ))
If I get him wrapped up in this,
he'll be expelled this time!
《ここでアニキを巻き込んだり
したら　今度は退学？》
Hey, Kazu...!
≪おい　カズ！≫
決まってんだろ
助けに行くんだよ！
There's only one thing to
do! I'm going to rescue her!
I can handle this all by myself.
オレ１人で充分だ。
あれ？
ダブ！
あ？
Huh?
わっ！
（坊主頭）ウッ…。
大丈夫だ　今のオレには
あの必殺技がある！
It'll be okay. Now I have
that special attack!
（坊主頭）ウッ…。
ウフッ！
Get away from Azusa!
梓から離れろ！
はぁ？
ウッ！
和くん？
Kazu-kun?
ハァハァ…。
ウッ！！
うわぁ！
（坊主頭）ウッ…ウッ！
う～…。
ウッ！ジョワッ！
Jowa!!
ウー！ウー…。
ア　ア…。
≪ま　まずい！≫
C-Crap...
Hey, Oga...
おい　男鹿！
Just watch.
見ててやろうぜ。
ウー！ウッ！
あぁ～っ！
I can't turn-tail now...
I have to save Azusa!
《ここで　ひるんじゃダメだ。
梓を助けなきゃ！》
梓！逃げろ～！！
Azusa, run for it!
え？和くん！
Kazu-kun?
ウッ！
ダァァーー！！
（坊主頭）ウッ！
あっ！
（山村）あぁ～っ！！
Kazu-kun, are you feeling all right?
和くん　大丈夫？
ちっ。しょうがねえなぁ。
What a pain.
ダメです！アニキ！
Don't do it, Brother!
This... I will handle...
ここは　オレが。ここはオレが
１人でやらなきゃ　いけないんです。
By myself...
I have to do this alone!
オレがこいつを倒す！
I'll beat this guy!
あぁぁぁ～～～！！
ちょっと　うるさいわね！
何やってんの？
Hey, pipe down out here!
What the hell are you doing?
Don't come too close! This guy is...
近付いたら　危ないっす。
こいつは…。
え？うちの　おじいちゃんの
知り合いだけど。
He's an acquaintance of
my grandfather, and...?
As I figured...
やはり…えっ！？
何つったんすか？
Huh? What was that?
You know him?
知り合い？
ここって　お前んち？
This is where you live?
ウッス！修業の途中で　こんな
デカイ山いもが　とれたんで→
Uosu!
During my training, I found this giant
wild potato and brought it here, uosu!
持ってきたっす。ウッス！
（邦枝）あ…ありがと。→
Uh, thanks...
ってか　声デカすぎ。
近所メーワク！
ウッス！
And can you speak more quietly?
You'll disturb the neighbors.
Uoisu!
That's what I mean!
それ！お…男鹿！
何これ　どういうこと？
O-Oga?
What? What's going on?!
はっ！実は道に迷ってしまい
彼女に案内して→
Actually I got lost!
This girl showed me here!
いただいたのであります。
ウォィッス！
Uoisu!
Hand the potato over.
（邦枝）イモ貸して。
（坊主頭）はっ！
Sure.
（ゴン！）
（邦枝）うるさい！
Shut up!
Aza~su!
（坊主頭）あざ～っす！
Sorry about the misunderstanding.
悪かったな。勘違いして。
Oh, don't worry about it.
いいんだよ　そんなの。でも
先輩ちの神社　ご利益はなかったな。
But I guess her shrine
didn't grant my prayer.
はぁ…何かカッコわりぃ。
That was so uncool...
Oh yeah? You might not
have gotten stronger...
そうかな？強くはなかったけど
和くん　カッコよかったよ！
But you were really cool, Kazu-kun!
（古市）いやぁ　まさかこの神社が
クイーンの実家だったとは！→
Wow! Who knew this shrine
would be the Queen's home?
Maybe I'll come and pray here every day!
オレ　毎日お参りに来ちゃおっかな！
いいから！
Whatever!
それでは　失礼！
Now then, if you'll excuse me!
That chrome-top's got one hell of a
nasty look to him, that's for sure.
つ～か　あの坊主　なにムダに
イカつい顔してんだよ。
ダー！
My grandfather isn't your
normal person either, so...
うちの　おじいちゃんも
変な人だから…。
By the way, Madame,
それにしてもお嬢さん　しばらく
見ぬ間に　きれいになって→
you have become quite pretty
since I saw you last!
And I hear you have a boyfriend?
彼氏までできて！
ち　違うから！
そんなんじゃないから！
T-That's not true! It's not like that!
The young lady~ has got a boyfriend~
♪～（坊主頭）お嬢さんにぃ
彼氏ができた～
Stop it!
（邦枝）やめて　もう！うるさい！
なんだ　ありゃ？
Shut up already!
What the heck?
ダーブ！
Watch out, Oga! Angelica-san
is coming to the Human World!
Angelica-san? Who was that again?
Alaindelon's daughter!
Why is she coming here?
Could it be she's going to live
in my house instead of Alaindelon?
Yople. Yopalelimen.
And the shocking return of the Yople Aliens?!
On the next Beelzebub:
Called a Magical Girl!
Plus Hilda-san and Kunieda-senpai
transform into magical girls?
I have no clue what the
plot is going to be about.